Let's just say, I'm glad you're here.
这么说吧, 真高兴你来这儿.
What's that singing?
那是谁在唱歌?
That is my roommate, Danny.
是我的室友. Danny.
Though at the moment, he's certainly not the guy I moved in with.
不过这会儿, 他当然不是当初那个和我一起搬进来的家伙.
Well, he's not the type who sings around the house.
Well, 他可不是那种在屋子里到处唱歌的人.
Lisa, you look ravishing this morning.
Lisa, 你今天早上简直是美艳动人.
Danny?
Are you one of those people that aliens abduct and take to their spaceships for experiments?
你是那种被外星人劫持到他们的宇宙飞船上,被他们做实验的人吗?
No, Why do you ask?
No, 你干吗这样问?
Look at you.
看看你自己吧.
Um, So. Danny, What's going on?
Um, So. Danny, 发生了什么事?
Ah, let's see. I. she, we...
Ah,让我想想, 我, 她, 我们...
-Ah, ha. -What?
My friend Hannah is a scuba diver.
我的朋友Hannah是个潜水员.
At this time of year?
在这个季节?
The ocean must be freezing.
海水肯定冷极了.
That's what the wet suit is for.
这就是为什么要穿湿式潜水服呀.
To keep you warm. But Danny,
这样可以保暖. 不过Danny,
it's not going to fit.
你穿这件不合身.
Now will someone please explain the bee suit?
谁能解释一下这套蜜蜂服又是怎么回事?
It's my job.
那是我的工作.
I don't believe it.
我才不信呢.
I deliver balloons at ten,
我10点钟去送气球,
then Hannah and I are off to the seashore.
然后Hannah和我就到海边去.
So things are going well, huh Danny?
那么一切都顺利了, huh Danny?
Lisa, Hannah is the first woman I can talk to completely unedited.
Lisa, Hannah是我碰到的第一个我可以完全不用隐瞒地与她交谈的女人.
A frightening thought.
可怕的想法.
Ah there we are. See you later.
Ah,在这儿呢. 回头见.
I want my old roommate back.
真希望我的室友能回到以前的样子.
Hey, it's good that Danny's happy, right?
Hey, 丹尼这么开心不是很好吗, 对不对?
Yes. I just wish he'd stop singing.
Yes. 我只是希望他别再唱歌了.